const STORE=[
  { id:0,
    question: 'What is the type of Pikachu?',
    choices:['Normal','Electric','Steel','Fairy'],
    answer:'Electric'
  },
  { id:1,
    question: 'What is the evolution of Pikachu?',
    choices:['Magikarp','Pichu','Raichu','Togedemaru'],
    answer:'Raichu'
  },
  { id:2,
    question: 'What is the second type of the Raichu evolved in Alola?',
    choices:['Fairy','Flying','Water','Psychic'],
    answer:'Psychic'
  },
  { id:3,
    question: 'What is the item that only affects Pikachu, and double its damage?',
    choices:['Magnet','Electric Seed','Light Ball','Zap Plate'],
    answer:'Light Ball'
  },
  { id:4,
    question: 'Which body character is different between female and male Pikachu?',
    choices:['The body stripe.','The electric pouches color.','The ear shape.','The tail shape.'],
    answer:'The tail shape.'
  },
  { id:5,
    question: 'What is the hidden ability of Pikachu?',
    choices:['Lighting Rod','Static','Electric Terrain','Volt Absorb'],
    answer:'Lighting Rod'
  },
  { id:6,
    question: 'What is the Z-move triggered by Pikanium Z?',
    choices:['Catastropika','10,000,000 Volt Thunderbolt','Volt Tackle','Gigavolt Havoc'],
    answer:'Catastropika'
  },
  { id:7,
    question: 'What is Pikachu’s species strengths (HP-Attack-Defense-Special Attack-Special Defense-Speed)?',
    choices:['55-50-35-40-50-90','35-55-40-50-50-90','45-40-50-50-35-100','40-55-35-50-40-100'],
    answer:'35-55-40-50-50-90'
  },
  { id:8,
    question: 'What is the steel type move that Pikachu learned in the animation?',
    choices:['Gyro Ball','Iron Tail','Meteor Mash','Iron Head'],
    answer:'Iron Tail'
  },
  { id:9,
    question: 'Which is the main color of the “shiny” Pikachu? (Note: The shiny pokemon is the rare pokemon that has a different color, encountered with probability 1/4096 in base case)',
    choices:['Yellow','Pink','Black','Orange'],
    answer:'Orange'
  }
]